<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SBRU Trip Manager</string>

    <string name="cancun_info">
     Habitaciones Incluye las habitaciones de tu elección.

    Actividades Actividades diarias conducidas por animadores. El programa varía diariamente.

    Impuestos y propinas Todos los impuestos y propinas están incluidos.

    Entretenimiento Incluye actividades diarias y noches de película. El programa varia diariamente.

    Alimentos y Bebidas Incluye los 3 alimentos: desayuno, comida y cena con buffet asistido además de snacks y barra libre de bebidas nacionales. Por el momento el servicio de room service se encuentra suspendido. Los alimentos a la carta tiene costo extra.

    Deportes Acuáticos Incluye actividades acuáticas tales como kayak y aerobics acuáticos.

    Deportes en tierra Los deportes en tierra incluyen voleibol, badminton y ping pong.

    Restricciones Por el momento existen restricciones en los horarios de los centros de consumo, a la llegada se entrega una hoja con la información.
    </string>

    <string name="miami_info">
      Situated on oceanfront Collins Avenue in the heart of Millionaire\'s Row, Fontainebleau Miami Beach is one
        of the most historically and architecturally significant hotels on Miami Beach, Florida. Its iconic design
        is a spectacular blend of Miami’s glamorous golden era and stylish modern luxury. A revered Miami Beach
        landmark for more than half a century, Morris Lapidus’ emblematic curvilinear building sets a new standard
        for business and pleasure. The 22-acre oceanfront Miami Beach hotel features signature restaurants by
        award-winning chefs; two chic nightlife venues; a two-story spa, a virtually endless poolscape, miles of
        pristine beach and state-of-the-art conference and event facilities.
    </string>

    <string name="puntacana_info">
        This hotel is centrally located in Punta Cana Village, 10 minutes’ drive from its private beach and just 2 km from Punta Cana International Airport. It features free Wi-Fi, a swimming pool and a gym.

        The Four Points by Sheraton Punta Cana Village offer air-conditioned rooms with modern décor, a desk, heating and cable TV. The bathrooms have shower and come with free toiletries.

        Free scheduled shuttle to the golf course La Cana, the Six Senses Spa, Punta Cana beach and the Punta Cana Nature Reserve.

        The guests at the Four Points can enjoy international cuisine at the Ara Restaurant. It is open from 6:30 am to 10:30 pm.

        This property is 15 minutes’ drive from the Manati Park and 20 minutes’ drive from Bavaro Beach. The Coral Motorway is 3 km away.

        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.1 for a two-person trip.

        We speak your language!
    </string>

    <string name="santamaria_info">
     Located in Marsala, Baglio Oneto Dei Principi Di San Lorenzo - Luxury Wine Resort is in a rural area and
        near the beach. Museo Archeologico di Baglio Anselmi and Museum of Salt are cultural highlights,
        and some of the area\'s notable landmarks include Riserva Naturale dello Stagnone and Mozia.
        Discover the area\'s water adventures with water skiing and windsurfing nearby, or enjoy the great
        outdoors with mountain biking and hiking/biking trails.
    </string>

    <string name="losangeles_info">
      Situated in Beverly Hills, this hotel is 12 minutes\' walk from shopping on Rodeo Drive. It features gourmet on-site dining options, a full-service spa and spacious guest rooms with flat-screen TVs.

        Cream colored rooms boast an iPod docking station at Beverly Hills The Peninsula. A microwave, refrigerator and minibar are available in all rooms.

        World-class dining for breakfast, lunch and dinner is available at the Belvedere restaurant. The Belvedere is a lively seafood-centric Mediterranean restaurant showcasing award-winning cuisine in a warm and inviting environment. The adjacent outdoor terrace space is a destination for al fresco dining under the glittering Beverly Hills evening sky.

        A large rooftop outdoor pool and a modern gym with personal coaches are available. Free WiFi is available throughout the hotel. Upon check-in guests can enjoy free fresh fruit and a welcome beverage. Shoe shining services are available.

        The University of California Los Angeles is 4 km from The Peninsula. Universal Studios is 13.4 km away.

        Couples particularly like the location — they rated it 9.3 for a two-person trip.

        We speak your language!
    </string>

    <string-array name="numPeople">
        <item> </item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="numRooms">
        <item> </item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>